[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is a correct syntax to output \"Hello World\" in C++?",
    "answers": [
      "System.out.println(\"Hello World\");",
      "Console.WriteLine(\"Hello World\");",
      "cout << \"Hello World\";",
      "print (\"Hello World\");"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "cout << \"Hello World\";"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "C++ is an alias of C#",
    "answers": ["False", "True"],
    "correctAnswer": "False"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "How do you insert COMMENTS in C++ code?",
    "answers": [
      "# This is a comment",
      "// This is a comment",
      "/* This is a comment"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "// This is a comment"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
    "answers": ["string", "myString", "String", "Txt"],
    "correctAnswer": "string"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
    "answers": ["double x = 5;", "int x = 5;", "num x = 5", "x = 5;"],
    "correctAnswer": "int x = 5;"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
    "answers": ["double x = 2.8;", "byte x = 2.8", "int x = 2.8;", "x = 2.8;"],
    "correctAnswer": "double x = 2.8;"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which method can be used to find the length of a string?",
    "answers": ["getLength()", "length()", "len()", "getSize()"],
    "correctAnswer": "length()"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which operator is used to add together two values?",
    "answers": ["The & sign", "The * sign", "The + sign"],
    "correctAnswer": "The + sign"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes.",
    "answers": ["False", "True"],
    "correctAnswer": "False"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which header file lets us work with input and output objects?",
    "answers": [
      "#include <iosstring>",
      "#include <inputstr>",
      "#include <stream>",
      "#include <iostream>"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "#include <iostream>"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
    "answers": ["<>", "=", "==", "><"],
    "correctAnswer": "=="
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "To declare an array in C++, define the variable type with:",
    "answers": ["[]", "()", "{}"],
    "correctAnswer": "[]"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Array indexes start with:",
    "answers": ["0", "1"],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "How do you create a function in C++?",
    "answers": [
      "functionName()",
      "functionName[]",
      "functionName.",
      "(functionName)"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "functionName()"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "How do you call a function in C++?",
    "answers": [
      "functionName[];",
      "functionName;",
      "functionName();",
      "(functionName);"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "functionName();"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a class in C++?",
    "answers": ["class", "className", "class()", "MyClass"],
    "correctAnswer": "class"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?",
    "answers": [
      "new myObj = MyClass();",
      "class MyClass = new myObj();",
      "MyClass myObj;",
      "class myObj = new MyClass();"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "MyClass myObj;"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "In C++, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswer": "True"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?",
    "answers": ["largest(x,y)", "max(x,y)", "maximum(x,y)", "maxNum(x,y)"],
    "correctAnswer": "max(x,y)"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Which operator is used to multiply numbers?",
    "answers": ["*", "#", "x", "%"],
    "correctAnswer": "*"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "How do you create a reference variable of an existing variable?",
    "answers": [
      "With the * operator",
      "With the ref word",
      "With the REF word",
      "With the & operator"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "With the & operator"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "How do you start writing an if statement in C++?",
    "answers": ["if x > y:", "if (x > y)", "if x > y then:"],
    "correctAnswer": "if (x > y)"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "How do you start writing a while loop in C++?",
    "answers": [
      "while x > y {",
      "while (x > y)",
      "while x > y:",
      "x > y while {"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "while (x > y)"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?",
    "answers": ["void", "get", "return", "break"],
    "correctAnswer": "return"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
    "answers": ["break", "stop", "exit", "return"],
    "correctAnswer": "break"
  }
]
